<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>907.life</title>
    <link>https://907.life/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 907.life</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://907.life/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://907.life/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://907.life/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-geoff-wright&#34;&gt;About Geoff Wright&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a husband and father of three living in Anchorage, Alaska, and the primary author of this site. I love snow, cross country skiing, biking, sailing, trails, books, general nerdery, trees, kindness, and Sunday morning pancakes. I was born in Iowa, and I&amp;rsquo;ve also lived in Nebraska, Massachusetts, and Maryland. I graduated from St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s College of Maryland with a BA in Philosophy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I owned Pango Technology, Inc., a software development firm, until 2023 when I sold my shares to my partners and partially retired. These days I dedicate my time to doing good in my community: working as a small business counselor with the Alaska Small Business Development Center, coaching cross country skiing at Bettye Davis East High School, and volunteering as a sailing instructor at the Alaska Sailing Club.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://907.life/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://907.life/welcome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This site provides practical guidance for living without a smartphone. I haven&amp;rsquo;t used one in three years, and I address the real challenges of smartphone-free living rather than offering quick fixes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;core-message&#34;&gt;Core Message&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The solution to your smartphone problems isn&amp;rsquo;t another hack, screen timer, or setting to tweak. I advocate removing the device entirely while maintaining normal social and professional life.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;who-this-is-for&#34;&gt;Who This Is For&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This site serves several groups:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
